<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Networking on</title><link>https://mskblackbelt.github.io/tags/networking/</link><description>Recent content in Networking on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>© 2025</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 15:38:56 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mskblackbelt.github.io/tags/networking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Creating a network share on Windows 7 (Pro) accessible from Windows NT 4.0</title><link>https://mskblackbelt.github.io/blog/network_share_nt_to_7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 15:38:56 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://mskblackbelt.github.io/blog/network_share_nt_to_7/</guid><description>&lt;p>A colleague and I set out to rid ourselves of floppy disks in the teaching labs. Several of the control computers in the teaching labs are pretty old, some still still running Windows NT 4.0. Because of software and hardware requirements, OS upgrades are out of the question, and USB and CD-RW support are non-existent in NT. But all the machines are equipped with ethernet, so we decided to set up a small LAN. The trickiest part of the process was getting to the realization that NT 4.0 didn&amp;rsquo;t come with the TCP/IP stack installed by default… we had to pull out the NT install discs and have Windows install that stack before we could communicate with other machines.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Safari No Connection</title><link>https://mskblackbelt.github.io/blog/safari-no-connection/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 14:44:53 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://mskblackbelt.github.io/blog/safari-no-connection/</guid><description>&lt;p>I just spent the past 45 minutes trying to troubleshoot an internet connection problem on my work computers… While trying to set up Tapbots new Mastodon client [Ivory][ivory], I couldn&amp;rsquo;t get the authentication page to load in Safari. My campus connection periodically experiences issues due to any number of things: campus network problems, campus IT problems, campus IT blocking my local router, problems with my local router,&lt;sup id="fnref:1">&lt;a href="#fn:1" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref">1&lt;/a>&lt;/sup> etc. In fact, I&amp;rsquo;ve been experiencing periodic issues all day.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>