<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Python on</title><link>https://mskblackbelt.github.io/tags/python/</link><description>Recent content in Python on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>© 2025</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 15:46:20 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mskblackbelt.github.io/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Comparison of NumPy and SciPy curve fitting algorithms</title><link>https://mskblackbelt.github.io/blog/curve_fitting_comparison/curve_fitting_comparison/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 15:46:20 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://mskblackbelt.github.io/blog/curve_fitting_comparison/curve_fitting_comparison/</guid><description>&lt;p>In an effort to reduce the number of concepts my students need to learn in Physical Chemistry lab, I&amp;rsquo;m trying to cut down the number of Python methods I introduce to them. One of the places where there are &lt;em>many&lt;/em> options is in the realm of curve fitting. For a simple linear fit, just SciPy and NumPy offer at least three separate options:&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Opening files with NumPy</title><link>https://mskblackbelt.github.io/blog/numpy_file_loading/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 14:30:13 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://mskblackbelt.github.io/blog/numpy_file_loading/</guid><description>&lt;p>A new tack I&amp;rsquo;m taking this semester is to remove the use of &lt;a href="http://pandas.pydata.org" target="_blank">Pandas&lt;/a> from my Physical Chemistry Lab course. Pandas is an excellent tool with &lt;em>many&lt;/em> evangelists. After some careful examination (and questions from a colleague), I realized that &lt;em>my&lt;/em> reasons for using it the course weren&amp;rsquo;t justified. For the most part, I was using Pandas because it made pretty outputs in a Jupyter notebook… hardly a good reason for introducing a new tool to students already overwhelmed with new tools. In an effort to teach the basics (in this case, Python with NumPy, SciPy, and Matplotlib), I decided to replace my Pandas calls with their more fundamental equivalents. None of this is to day Pandas isn&amp;rsquo;t an excellent tool, only that I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to use very limited course time to teach an additional tool (and introduce more sources of confusion).&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Hello Website</title><link>https://mskblackbelt.github.io/blog/hello-website/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 14:21:20 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://mskblackbelt.github.io/blog/hello-website/</guid><description>&lt;h2 class="relative group">The site
&lt;div id="the-site" class="anchor">&lt;/div>
&lt;span
class="absolute top-0 w-6 transition-opacity opacity-0 ltr:-left-6 rtl:-right-6 not-prose group-hover:opacity-100">
&lt;a class="group-hover:text-primary-300 dark:group-hover:text-neutral-700"
style="text-decoration-line: none !important;" href="#the-site" aria-label="Anchor">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/span>
&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This site is meant to be a brain dump for the assorted projects and task I take on at Hunter College. I will likely end up being a collection of comments, tips and tricks for specific instruments, and rundowns of my experiences with instrumentation in various states of disrepair. Most of the content is meant to be an easy reference for myself, but hopefully someone else finds bits of it useful.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>