<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Musings and Notes</title><link>https://mskblackbelt.github.io/blog/</link><description>Recent content on Musings and Notes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mskblackbelt.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>TIL– Making your own cable (_not_ coax!)</title><link>https://mskblackbelt.github.io/blog/wire-sleeving/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mskblackbelt.github.io/blog/wire-sleeving/</guid><description>While listening to the 2016 Christmas Shopping Show of The Ham Radio Workbench podcast, I learned about components for making your own wire. One of the hosts mentions that he keeps around &amp;ldquo;bus wire and spaghetti&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Safari No Connection</title><link>https://mskblackbelt.github.io/blog/safari-no-connection/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 14:44:53 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://mskblackbelt.github.io/blog/safari-no-connection/</guid><description>I just spent the past 45 minutes trying to troubleshoot an internet connection problem on my work computers… While trying to set up Tapbots new Mastodon client [Ivory][ivory], I couldn&amp;rsquo;t get the authentication page to load in Safari.</description></item><item><title>Thermal Runaway error on Creality Ender 3 Neo</title><link>https://mskblackbelt.github.io/blog/ender3-thermal-runaway/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mskblackbelt.github.io/blog/ender3-thermal-runaway/</guid><description>Just before Christmas, I purchased a Creality Ender 3 Neo (v1) printer on discount. Up to now, I&amp;rsquo;ve been working with a Monoprice Select Mini Pro (purchased at the start of the pandemic so I could work on 3D modeling projects at home…).</description></item><item><title>Migrating the site to Hugo</title><link>https://mskblackbelt.github.io/blog/site-move-hugo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 14:21:20 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://mskblackbelt.github.io/blog/site-move-hugo/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to migrate my site from Lektor to Hugo. This is solely because Hugo seems to have far more community surrounding it. I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;m ever going to dig far enough into my site to muck with or redesign the core generator, so having a Python-based SSG doesn&amp;rsquo;t make sense as a decision point.</description></item><item><title>TIL – How to edit sketch patterns in Fusion360</title><link>https://mskblackbelt.github.io/blog/f360-sketch-pattern/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 14:21:20 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://mskblackbelt.github.io/blog/f360-sketch-pattern/</guid><description>While mocking up a sample holder, I wanted to go back and edit a pattern object that was embedded in a sketch. Since sketch actions don&amp;rsquo;t appear in the history scrubber (one item for the entire sketch), I couldn&amp;rsquo;t go to my default action of right-click&amp;gt;Edit on the object in the history scrubber.</description></item><item><title>TIL – Linking (and attaching) a local image in Lektor</title><link>https://mskblackbelt.github.io/blog/lektor-attach-image/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 14:21:20 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://mskblackbelt.github.io/blog/lektor-attach-image/</guid><description>While trying to post the previous item, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t get the local image to display. I tried placing the PNG file in the post folder with the contents.lr file, then linking with !</description></item><item><title>Website publication</title><link>https://mskblackbelt.github.io/blog/site-publication/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 14:21:20 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://mskblackbelt.github.io/blog/site-publication/</guid><description>GitHub Pages> GitHub Pages # This site is hosted using GitHub Pages, a hosting service available to all GitHub accounts (for free!). Setting up Lektor to deploy to GitHub is very simple once you&amp;rsquo;ve configured your machine to connect to GitHub using an SSH connection.</description></item><item><title>Hello Website</title><link>https://mskblackbelt.github.io/blog/hello-website/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 14:21:20 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://mskblackbelt.github.io/blog/hello-website/</guid><description>The site> The site # This site is meant to be a brain dump for the assorted projects and task I take on at Hunter College. I will likely end up being a collection of comments, tips and tricks for specific instruments, and rundowns of my experiences with instrumentation in various states of disrepair.</description></item></channel></rss>